# Siddu Hosageri

Digital Marketing Manager

siddu.hosageri@gmail.com

9740080004

### Summary

A strategic digital marketing professional with extensive experience in promotional initiatives, analyzing market trends, discovering new markets and generating new sales leads. A results-driven innovator in digital marketing.

Skills: Digital Marketing Strategy, Business Development, Analytical Skills, Team Management, Vendor Negotiations,

Professional Experience: SEO, Paid Advertising, Email Marketing, Social Media Marketing & Management, Website Optimization, Digital Content Creation, Content Curation, and Business & Digital Analyst

# Experience

#### Digital Marketing Manager at Fazlani Natures Nest

April 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months) Pune, Maharashtra, India

- Development and execution of Digital strategy and media planning (SEO, SEM, Social Media, Google Ads, Data Analytics)
- Development of Branding and Loyalty strategy.
- Comprehensive management for Customer Service and Customer Experience. Leadership in implementation of CRM project and Campaign Management.
- Sales focused on consistent target achievement using Marketing Qualified Leads generated through online channels and partnerships.

Digital marketing strategies have resulted in 65% revenue contribution in overall revenue of Fazlani Natures Nest with less than 8% of cost within one year of operation.

# Assistant Digital Marketing Manager at Niraamaya Retreats

November 2013 – April 2019 (5 years 6 months)

As a Digital Marketing Manager, I develop digital engagement strategies and tactics as part of an integrated marketing and media plan to support overall Niraamaya Retreats marketing goals and objectives. These strategies and tactics include Branding, Social media marketing, Search engine optimization, Display advertising, Designing and other existing and new opportunities across web, mobile, and other developing channels.

- Responsible to drive all digital marketing initiatives for Niraamaya Retreats in luxury wellness and leisure segment.
- Manage the property websites, online content management tools, content on all owned platforms as well as on social media platforms.
- Strategize and develop action plans to drive digital revenue for rooms and secondary revenue streams.
- Monitor performance of all paid media campaigns (Google Adwords, Facebook, Display etc).
- Manage social media channels to build brand reputation and loyalty through relevant and engaging content.

• Strategize and create artworks for online and offline marketing activities and all hotel related creatives.

### **Account Manager - Digital Marketing**

Soppnox Communication Media Pvt Ltd

May 2012 - September 2013 (1 year 5 months) Bangalore

Handling key accounts. Coordinating with Web developers, Graphic designers, and content writers in developing a digital presence for clients.

- Develop a website traffic plan and create goals and benchmarks to meet
- Generate monthly reports on our marketing campaign's performance
- Partner with advertising and media specialists to increase marketing results
- Handling official social media platforms (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Youtube)
- Strong understanding of Search Engine Marketing -SEM (AdWords) and SEO
- Managing digital campaigns

# **Account Manager - Digital Marketing**

CrossWorks

November 2010 - April 2012 (1 year 6 months) Bengaluru,

Handling key accounts. Coordinating with Web developers, Graphic designers, and content writers in developing a digital presence for clients.

- Develop a website traffic plan and create goals and benchmarks to meet
- Generate monthly reports on our marketing campaign's performance
- Partner with advertising and media specialists to increase marketing results
- Handling official social media platforms (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Youtube)
- Strong understanding of Search Engine Marketing -SEM (AdWords) and SEO
- Managing digital campaigns

#### Sales Executive - Online Courses

Siliconindia

December 2008 - November 2010 (2 years) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Responsible for inbound marketing of Online Courses through online media channels

#### Certification:

Google adwords,

Fundamental of Digital Marketing - Google

#### Education

**Bangalore University** 

MBA, Marketing, 2006 - 2008

Karnatak University

BBA, Marketing, 2003 - 2006